[Music]
[Música]
Pay attention to this move, okay, story that
atentos a esta movida vale historia que
you've seen of a guy getting into
habéis visto de un tipo metiéndose en
a fight on YouTube with these people from yesterday,
una pelea de Youtube con estos de ayer
okay, a lady telling him I'm glad
vale una señora diciéndole me alegro
basically that your
básicamente de que se haya muerto tu
daughter died. I mean, you have the Justice of heaven,
hija O sea tienes la Justicia del cielo
not the condemnation that heaven has given you,
no la condena que el cielo te ha dado
well for Peppa this would be Sister
pues para para la Peppa este sería Sor
Gossip. I mean, no, the other one this would be Sister
Cotilla O sea no el otro este sería Sor
Gossip for the ppppa, okay, pay attention to the
Cotilla para la pppa vale atenta la
defense because the ppppa are totally
defensa que a la pppa eh totalmente
sure and if juanju at some point, yes, yes, if
segura y si juanju en algún momento si
this reaches him, he wants to
si le si le llega esto quiere quiere
rectify me, let me rectify myself. I'm
rectificar me que me rectifique yo estoy
totally sure that he didn't mean
totalmente Segura que no se refería
because it's not his profile. no, no, it's not
porque no es el perfil de él no no no es
the profile of him who goes to his girlfriend but to
el perfil de é que va a su chica sino a
her herself. In this story that you've
ella en sí en esta historia que habéis
seen it's not Juan's profile, hon, to
visto que no es el perfil de Juan hón
do these things and these types of
hacer estas cosas y este tipo de
comments, okay, Peppa. Here it was.
comentarios vale Peppa Aquí sí lo era
Look, this was when the love thing, romeira,
Mira Esto fue cuando lo de amor romeira
who is your friend. Do you remember what he said? What
que es tu amiga Te acuerdas lo que dijo
offended you a lot? Do you
que te ofendió mucho lo que dijo te
remember what Juano said about love?
acuerdas lo que dijo Juano sobre amor
What love  he had to send a
que amor le tuvo que mandar un
statement telling him that he would delete it
comunicado diciéndole que borraba
quickly or he would eliminate it or he would eliminate it
rapidito o o lo eliminaba o lo eliminaba
Or he would report it what's going on
O lo denunciaba qué pasa
Marinilla okay daughter you tell me
marinilla vale hija tú me vas contando
my sister exactly says Marina says
mi herma exactamente dice Marina dice
Marina be careful with undervaluing
Marina que cuidado con infravalorar
telesalseo and the celebrities that come here
telesalseo y los famosos que vienen aquí
because because in fact
porque porque de hecho por aquí han
half the gossip press have passed through here I've already come in
pasado media prensa del corazón Ya entre
here the main channel have
aquí el canal principal por aquí han
passed through here you know well he apologizes because he
pasado sabes bueno pide disculpas porque
messed up This is what you were saying
se ha cagado Esto es lo que decías tú
Peppa about Juanjo when the love thing
Peppa de Juanjo cuando lo de amor
romeira apologizes because he
romeira pide disculpas porque se ha
messed up not because he's sorry we all
cagado no porque lo sienta todos lo
know him already Ah you knew him there Peppa you
conocemos ya Ah ahí lo conocías Peppa
knew him there Yes yes Juan Ju has already crossed
ahí lo conocías Sí sí Juan Ju ha cruzado
the red line a while ago this is a
ya la línea roja hace tiempo esto es un
tet of yours Peppa a TT of yours So the
tet tuyo Peppa un TT tuyo Entonces el
profile gives the profile or it doesn't give the profile
perfil da el perfil o no da el perfil
Peppa it depends No if we have to
Peppa depende No si nos tenemos que
approach Javi Oliveira to collaborate
acercar a Javi oliveira para colaborar
in the Corrillo Oh there Ju was very bad
en el Corrillo Ay ahí Ju era muy malo
now since we don't have Jai Oliveira or
ahora ya que no tenemos Jai oliveira ni
anyone from the environment there I'll adapt to whatever it is
nadie del entorno ahí ya me acoplo a lo
then Answer this Peppa because
que sea pues Contéstale a este Peppa que
this one is looking for you Not me the others one
este si te está buscando Yo no los demás
thing a fool a fool of an
una cosa un tonto un tonto de de un
enemy of mine be faithful you that
enemigo mío sea fide tú que se va la
Pepa is going to the space of RAE of legum passes of of
[__] al space de RAE de legum pasa de de
all the harassers of all the
de todos los acosadores de todo la
association against Javi an enemy of mine
asociación contra Javi un enemigo mío
that er before a friend that before the friend eh He does
que er ante amigo que ante el amigo eh
n't stop telling his community He doesn't
No para de decirle a su comunidad No
stop telling his community that I that
para de decir a su comunidad que yo que
I went to look for you and that's why you that I went to look for you and that's why
yo fui a buscarte y por eso tú que yo
you came to me
fui a buscarte y por eso tú viniste a mi
to my live and that's why you came to my
a mi directo y por eso tú viniste a mi
live Thank you peace a kiss Oh now that I do
directo Gracias paz un beso Ay ahora que
n't forget about peace that I have an
no se me olvide lo de paz que tengo
important message for the people of
mensaje importante para la gente de
Valencia to see RAE that there is a foolish
valencia a ver RAE que hay un tonto
enemy of mine who used to be a friend who didn't stop
enemigo mío que antes era amigo que no
telling his community that I was
para decir a su comunidad que yo te
chasing you so that you would come to me to my
perseguía para que viniese a a mi a mi
channel Ah I wouldn't have minded going to
canal Ah no me hubiera importado ir a
look for you to the end of the world Oh of course
buscarte al fin del mundo Oh claro que
not whatever it takes for your bones I die
no lo que haga falta por tus hueso muero
but it wasn't like that it was that you came in
pero no fue así fue que entraste tú un
here one day to the live and we already made this
día aquí al directo y ya hicimos esta
kind of cordial friendship
especie de amistad cordial amistad
cordial friendship is that like that or not totally false I
cordial es así o no totalmente falso Yo
arrived alone he arrived alone to the space
llegué solo él llegó solo al espacio
But well let's go because This goes for  me
Pero bueno vamos porque Esto va por mí
when did I say to you when did
cuándo he dicho yo a a vosotras cuándo
I say to you that this lady was
he dicho yo a vosotras que esta señora
stalking RAE to get into her
perseguía a RAE para que entrase en su
channel and you have a cordial friendship that doesn't
canal y tenés amistad cordial que no
just remain friendship mind you I think there's more
solo qued amistad ojo creo que hay más
but not on the side that you think very well well
pero no por el lado que pensáis muy bien
let's put it here there so they can
pues vamos a ponerlo aquí ahí para que
take the screenshot let's see de Troya eh
cojan el pantallazo a ver a de Troya eh
take the screenshot that idiot okay
coge el pantallazo ese tontuelo vale
idiot Alright well let's put it
idiota Muy bien pues vamos a ponerlo
here there so they can take the screenshot let's
aquí ahí para que cojan el pantallazo a
see ar rroa eh take the screenshot that
ver ar rroa eh coge el pantallazo ese
idiot let's see let's see idiot okay
tontuelo a ver a ver tontuelo vale
idiot I'll take the screenshot what do I
idiota yo te cojo el pantallazo qué
have to say what is totally false
tengo que decir totalmente falso lo que
what you're saying is
está lo que tú estás diciendo es
totally false What is true silly
totalmente falso Lo que sí es cierto
idiot the Juan jbl chain and aoc
tontuela tontuelo la cadena Juan jbl y
comes aok eh Lili is yours You can
viene aoc aok eh Lili es tuyo Tú puedes
do whatever you want the c issue
hacer lo que tú quieras el tema de los c
is the problem Ah the cl issue is the
es el problema Ah el tema de los cl el
problem Ah for my chill I'm not going to
problema Ah por mi chill yo no voy a
be behind eh I'm talking to you with Elton and
estar detrás eh Te hablo con Elton y
you come behind And he's there pick shovel pick pick pick shovel pick
vienes detrás Y está ahí pico pala picoa
shovel see how  you put
pico pala pico palala ves cómo metes
[ __ ] apart from putting [ __ ] that's
[__] aparte de metiendo [__] eso
also true eh you go to another place
también es verdad eh vas para otro sitio
egun happens we haven't heard about
egun pasa no hemos escuchado hablar de
gun man has done a man has
gun hombre me ha hecho una hombre me ha
done a raide to me lfj What's up What's up FJ
hecho una raide lfj Qué pasa Qué pasa FJ
What's up my boy thank you very much Hey
Qué pasa mi niño muchísimas gracias Oye
a kiss to all of you who come around
un besito a todos los que vengáis por
there on FJ No, you were already there
ahí por el FJ No qué estabas ya por ahí
criticizing people not what I
criticando a la gente no a lo que te
sent you you weren't you were criticizing
mandé no estabas estabas criticando a
those I sent you or what's up when you
los que te mandé o no pasa cuando ya
're already in the chat stretching the
estás metido en el chat tendiendo los
threads if we already know you eh There's no channel
hilos si ya te conocemos eh No hay canal
where there can be something that you
donde puede haber algo de que tú no
and your son don't try to get into because we
intentes meterte tú y tu hijo porque lo
're seeing it now it's Rael's turn but
estamos viendo ahora la toca a rael pero
on top of that Rael will soon
es que encima rael Próximamente
discover that he left man Noa Thank you very much
descubrirá que dejó hombre Noa Muchas
sweetheart Thank you very much
gracias corazón Muchísimas gracias
beautiful Dallas left Dallas and left
guapísima a Dallas dejó a Dallas y dejó
Javi and hooked up with Peppa who is
a Javi y enganchó a la Peppa que es peor
even worse than the other two together watch out
todavía que los otros dos juntos ojo
How how how did he say wait it's that they
Cómo cómo cómo ha dicho espérate es que
are mixing here lords Uncle Gustavo
están mezclando aquí lores tío Gustavo
talk to Fran so that he takes some of
habla con Fran para que acoja algunos de
these in the sanctuary  Yes in the
estos en el santuario Sí en el reptili
Aryan reptile in the Aryan reptile right be
ario en el reptili ario razón tenele
indiscreet they are feeding
indiscreta que le están dando de comer
the cap for talking about him let's see I am
al gorra por hablar de él a ver yo soy
of the philosophy eh Well the fact is that
de la filosofía eh Bueno es que de hecho
here we are not even two days old and and
aquí estamos no llevamos dos días y y
many times we talk about
muchas ocasiones hablamos de gente
Random people I am of the philosophy of Eh not to
Random Yo soy de la filosofía de Eh no
go around with that nonsense of Oh I'm not
andar con la tontería de esa de Ay no
going to mention this one because he has
voy a mencionar a este porque tiene
few followers And then if I talk about
pocos seguidores Y entonces si hablo de
him I feed him and And I give him
él le doy de comer y Y le doy
viewers I am I am not of that
espectadores yo soy yo no soy de esa
philosophy because in the end you deprive yourself
filosofía porque al final te privas tú
of content I am of the philosophy that I don't care
de contenido Yo soy de la filosofía de
if I have to make a
que me da igual si tengo que hacer un
video of a Random or a live of a
vídeo de un Random o un directo de de un
Random if it entertains us and that for people
Random si nos divierte y eso a la gente
because Ah I think it depends on the
porque Ah yo creo que depende de las
news of the heart that I make, you are
noticias del corazón que haga os
more interested or not I mean I think that yes we
interesan más o no O sea yo creo que que
can comment a little not on what
sí podemos comentar un poco no lo que ha
Anabel said now I am going to connect you
dicho Anabel ahora os voy a sa conectar
Anabel Pantoja when I feel like it now
Anabel Pantoja cuando me apetezca ahora
in a while everything else I don't know what
dentro de un rato todo lo otro no sé qué
But in the end you like eh here
Pero al final ustedes os gusta eh aquí
The salsita the chimor reillo no and many
La salsita el chimor reillo no y muchas
sometimes these geeks these characters
veces los frikis estos los personajes
Although they themselves do not have a large
estos Aunque ellos en sí no tengan mucho
audience Juanjo lard de Troya la Loli
público el Juanjo lard de Troya la Loli
these people do like you because they
esta gente em sí que os gusta porque se
create good gossip many times
montan buenos salseos muchas veces están
the gossip of these people is better than that
mejor los salseos de esta gente que los
of TV or reality shows okay
de la tele o los de un reality vale
even if they are unknown and apart from that they are exclusive to
aunque sean desconocidos y aparte son
us they are exclusive to
exclusivos nuestros son lores exclusivos
us because we are the ones with the largest
nuestros porque somos los que más
audience commenting on this topic let's
audiencia tenemos comentando este tema
say no no eh that gives them a bit
digamos no no eh que eso les da un poco
of audience well Okay but the
de audiencia bueno Vale pero en el
moment we stop talking about it they
momento que dejamos de hablar de ello ya
stop eh I mean the pppa had 100
ya paran eh o sea la pppa estaba con 100
viewers until we
espectadores hasta que hemos vuelto a
talked about it again you know Then I see that I
hablar de ella sabes Entonces eso lo veo
see it as a very poor mind That of not
una lo veo una mente muy pobre Eso de no
mentioning And this and that I see it as a
mencionar Y esto y lo otro lo veo una
very poor mind Come on you are not going to
mente muy pobre Hala tampoco le vas a
pay attention to any fool who comes out
dar bola a cualquier papanatas que salga
super shameless that he is doing it
super descarado que lo está haciendo
so that you mention it and answer him you
para que lo menciones y le contestes me
understand there are many people who make
entiendes hay mucha gente que me hace
videos of me that notice it is very shameless that it is
vídeo que nota muchísimo descarado que
to reappear on the map you
es para para reaparecer en el mapa me
understand Then it goes it is going to close
entiendes Entonces ya va ya va a cerrar
directly Javi le  come on, let's see,
directo Javi le pasa la audiencia a ver
wait, let me look at it
a ver espérate déjame que lo mire
completely right now We're the same the
totalmente ahora mismo Estamos iguales
moment it happens, now close it, keep an
en el momento que le pase ya Ya cierra
eye on that Who has been Who has
estate pendiente de eso Quién ha sido
been, monce, keep an eye on that, you'll
Quién ha sido monce t pendiente de eso
see How is it like that, well, let me
verá Cómo es así bueno dejarme que
listen to this, let's see, you
escuche esto a ver todavía que lo otas
two together, watch Jai and he hooked Peppa, he
dos juntos ojo Jai y enganchó a la Peppa
left Dallas and he left Javi and he hooked
dejó a Dalas y dejó a Javi y enganchó a
Peppa because we're seeing it now it's
la Peppa porque lo estamos viendo ahora
Raed's turn but on top of that,
le ha toca a raed pero es que encima
now it's Raed's turn Raed He'll
ahora le ha tocado a raed raed
soon discover that he left
Próximamente descubrirá que dejó a
Dallas Oh, okay, friendship, he means
Dallas Ah vale de amistad se refiere de
friendship, he left Dallas and he left Javi and
amistad dejó a Dallas y dejó a Javi y
hooked Peppa, who is worse, he left
enganchó a la Peppa que es peor dejó a
Dallas and he left Javi and hooked
Dallas y dejó a Javi y enganchó a la
Peppa, even more than the other two together,
Peppa todavía que los otras dos juntos
watch Peppa is worse than the other two
ojo que la Peppa es peor que los otros
together, eh, silly girl, that's not
dos juntos eh tontuela eso tampoco es
true either. Well, if he gets to know you a
verdad Bueno pues cu te conozca un
little bit more, he'll regret it, he'll
poquito más se arrepentirá se
regret it, he'll meet the lady who goes
arrepentirá conocerá a la señora que va
everywhere and never goes
por todos los sitios y nunca va
selflessly, I've already  echoed No, I
desinteresadamente ya me he hecho eco No
already answered you, are you happy? Well,
ya te respondi estás contenta Bueno
I hope that RAE figures it out soon and leaves you.
espero que RAE te cale pronto y te deje
You're wrong, it seems to me that he
estáis equivocado a mí me parece que
's with more, hey, I must have it wrong.
está con con más él eh lo tendré yo mal
No. Ah, okay, well, he's going to close, he's going to
no Ah vale pues ya va a cerrar ya va a
close, he's going to close, he's going to close. You'll
cerrar ya va a cerrar ya va a cerrar ya
see it in retrospect like time. I
lo Vais a ver atrás como el tiempo a mí
don't need to go looking for anyone.
no me hace falta de ir a buscar a nadie
No,
no
no, you don't need to. Look for anyone. You're
no no te hace falta Buscar a nadie estás
always after everyone. That's what
detrás de todo el mundo siempre eso
she would like you to talk about her. If
quisiera ella que tú hablara de ella si
the only reason is to defend what she
la noma encima es para defender lo que
does, no, no, but on top of that, you defend her.
hac no no pero es que encima la
Look at how that's not done.
defiendes mira como de Eso no se hace
Olga, no, no, it's not done when he
Olga de eso no no se hace cuando la ha
defended her from that, no. Hey, but if he
defendido de eso no Oye pero si r que
puts the clin. No, it's not as easy to
ponga el clin No no es tan fácil de
prove as it is easy to prove the
demostrar como tan fácil de demostrar el
role of the donation. I mean, exactly
papel de La donación digo yo exactamente
when Rael told him Rael about
cuando rael le has contado rael ya lo de
the 240, which were finally 250, Rael is
los 240 que finalmente eran 250 a rael
going to tell Ra, Ra he's going to
le va a contar a ra a ra le va a
care about the
importar lo de los
240, Ra for Ra, the 240. F, what is it? Let's
240 ra para ra los 240 F tú lo que es
go RAE  he doesn't mess around with those little things
vamos RAE no se anda con esas mijitas
RAE is more
RAE es más
than RAE is more than 2
de RAE es más de 2
240,000 ra is going to tell him about the 240 and the
240.000 ra le va a decir de los 240 y el
other one is going to say what the [ __ ] is that and
otro va a decir esa qué [__] [__] es y
what did you run to
qué fuiste corriendo a
[Laughs]
[Risas]
return it f
devolverlo f
you F t la Ray with that
tu F t la Ray con esa
pain Oh Sara we had to open cho
pena Ay Sara teníamos que abrir cho
Corrillo today but I didn't
Corrillo hoy pero es que no me he
remember daughter I didn't remember I didn't remember I don't believe it
acordado hija Es que no me he acordado
Mara I don't believe it you
acordado no me lo creo María no me lo
're kidding me already cut it out you
creo me estás vacilando ya corto no me
're not telling me as a joke [ __ ] joke [ __ ] joke [ __ ] joke [ __ ] joke no no no no no no no no
lo estás diciendo de broma [__] broma
no you
broma no no no no no no no no no me me
've trolled me you've trolled me
habéis troleado me habéis troleado
account or that's what you've taken
cuenta o eso lo que te has cogido
lately that I echoed the
últimamente que yo me hice eco de del
tweet of this Joe Hunter about the
tweet de de este de Joe Hunter de los
250 Hello Valentina Garca that's what
250 Hola Valentina García eso es lo que
you've cooked up my daughter it's a shame with
te has cocido hija mía es una pena con
all the Super chats they made you about
todos los Super chat que te hicieron de
240 that I lost 10 in each one of them let's
240 que perdiese 10 en cada uno de ellos
see how you explain it to your new
a ver cómo le explicas tú a tu recién
acquaintance  friend that friendship that you are
conocido amigo esa amistad que está
making now how do I explain to him that as of
haciendo ahora cómo le explic que a
today he has not taken out the little paper that
fecha de hoy no ha sacado el papelito
you promised so much that then
que tanto prometiste que luego
finally you said I will not take it out because I do not feel like it
finalmente dijiste no lo saco porque no
but the thing is that eloria
me da la gana pero es que es que eloria
is assuming that you
está dando por hecho que eso se lo
tell that to the ra and the raay gets offended it is that it is
cuentas al ra y al raay le ofende es que
tremendous or rather it is that it is tremendous eh Maybe
es tremendo o sea es que es tremendo eh
he shows it to him and then
A lo mejor él se lo enseña y luego le
explains to him how you tried to knock down a
explica cómo intentaste tumbar una
friendship from behind by spreading [ __ ] that you
amistad por detrás metiendo [__] que
almost managed to break the friendship see
casi lo consigues romper la amistad ves
explaining all that to your new friend
explicándole todo eso a tu nuevo amigo
known that cordial friendship Hello Susana
conocido esa amistad cordial Hola Susana
Rubi I would not feed those people no
Rubí yo no daría de comer a esa gente no
but it is that you have to answer her from time to
pero es que hay que responderla de vez
time because as she does not take a step
en cuando porque como ella no da un paso
look at her to confront Javi
mira ella para enfrentarse con Javi
Oliveira to confront anyone she has
oliveira para enfrentarse con cualquiera
not always put any of
siempre no ha metido por medio alguno de
us in the middle is that true what she is
nosotros eso es verdad lo que está
saying that of all It is true when we
diciendo que de to Es verdad cuando
were LoL she put us in the
estábamos LoL yo nos metía a nosotros
middle when we did not put the
por medio cuando no nosotr metido al
son in now she is putting RAE against
hijo ahora está metiendo a RAE en contra
me she always grabs on to someone she uses
mía siempre se agarra a alguien lo pone
as a parapet so that the host  someone
de parapeto para que la [__] se la
else takes it and she takes the 240 240
lleve otro y ella se lleva los 240 240
240 that happens because of those who carry and bring
240 eso pasa por los que llevan y trae
Antonio if he told ra that he told her I will
Antonio si se lo dijo a ra que se lo
explain it to her in his own way he showed her
dijo se lo explicaré a su manera le
the
enseñó el
paper he told RAE in his own way
papel se lo dijo a RAE a su manera
saying that it was a lie of mine at
diciendo que era mentira mía al
first now he is beginning to see but come on
principio ahora empieza a ver pero vamos
this one is taking it for granted as
es que este está dando por hecho como
if RAE eh if he finds out about the pppa
que RAE eh si se entera de lo de la pppa
like he won't know you know eh but
como que no lo sabrá ya sabes eh pero
this one is taking it for granted that r is going to be
este está dando por hecho que r se va a
offended by 240 F you with what
ofender por 240 F tú con lo que ha hecho
he has done with the cryptocurrencies Flower ridiculous
él en las criptomonedas Flower ridícula
and the blonde from Argentina is also a
y la rubia de argentinas también es un
little ridiculous on top of that silly he is a
pelín ridícula encima tontuelo es un
silly enemy of mine kante was a friend No
tonto enemigo mío kante era amigo No
daughter no I was a friend you have never been
hija no yo era amigo tú nunca has sido
friends with anyone Loli neither mine nor anyone
amiga de nadie Loli ni mía ni de nadie
You have no other relatives than your
Tú no tienes más parientes que son tus
teeth and there are people who and and they are false
dientes y hay gente que y y son postizos
simply a friend of mine kante was a friend No
simplemente amigo mío kante era amigo No
daughter no I was a friend you have never been
hija no yo era amigo tú nunca has sido
friends with anyone Loli neither mine nor anyone You
amiga de nadie Loli ni mía ni de nadie
have no other relatives than your
Tú no tienes más parientes que son tus
teeth there are people who and and they are false simply a friend of mine kante was a friend  people who simply
dientes hay gente que simplemente nos
meet in the world of course
encontramos en el mundo claro por
unfortunately Which by the way on Wednesday you already
desgracia Que por cierto el miércoles ya
know that with Agus we have the first eh
sabéis que tenemos con Agus primer eh
podcast of the season to talk about
podcast de la temporada para hablar de
very interesting things but Agus is not
cosas muy interesantes pero Agus no es
RAE's girlfriend Agus is RAE's girlfriend
la novia de RAE Agus es la novia de RAE
no RAE's girlfriend is going to start
no la novia de RAE se va a poner a
collaborating with It's that I this I this I can't
colaborar con Es que yo esto yo esto no
do but family you don't
puedo hacer pero familia ustedes no
think that I am Walt Disney or Stan
pensáis que yo soy Walt Disney o Stan
Lee I mean not because of the cameos
Lee O sea ya no por ya no por los cameos
and the mustache but because In
y por el bigote sino por es que En qué
what life or I mean in what life was Peppa going to get
en qué vida o sea en qué vida se iba a
together a
juntar la Peppa una concursante de gran
failed Big Brother contestant who on top of that YouTube has arrived
hermano fracasada que encima ha llegado
and has done her mischief her 240 her this her that
YouTube y ha hecho sus tropelías sus 240
with with Agus that Agus
su esto su lo otro con con Agus que Agus
is the girlfriend of a Venezuelan who was a
es la novia de un venezolano que era
friend of Dallas and they made a
amigo del Dallas que hicieron una meme
Coin meme that caused the biggest mess with the
Coin que se lió lo más grande con la
cryptocurrency Well the girlfriend I mean
criptomoneda Bueno pues la novia o sea
the unions don't make any sense I mean it's like suddenly she gets
las uniones o sea es como si de repente
together it's that I don't know how to tell you what
se junta es que no sé decirte qué
example it's like suddenly
ejemplo es como si de repente se junta a
Dara from Big Brother gets together with  the rock I mean it does
dara de gran hermano con la roca O sea
n't make sense Javi we live in the
no tiene sentido Javi vivimos en el
metaverse of gossip Yeah but it's like
metaverso del salseo Sí pero es como que
I'm not the ones they're unions that I
yo los uno no son son uniones que yo
create I mean it can't be more wonderful they
creo O sea no puede ser más maravilloso
owe me their lives eh They owe me their lives eh I
me deben la vida eh Me deben la vida eh
mean it's like if you put the one from Troy
o sea es como si juntas a al de Troya
with Brad Pitt maybe if I fight with Brad
con Brad Pitt capaz si me peleo con Brad
Pitt what happens it doesn't make sense it's
Pitt lo pasa sea no tiene sentido que es
the least logical thing in the world they are
lo menos lógico del mundo son
communities that have nothing to do
comunidades que no tienen nada que ver
with each other that are going to be
la una con la otra que nos van a venir a
very good for all of us Who is Agus
todos y a todas muy bien Quién es Agus
I hope it's not raab's girlfriend p I
Espero que no sea la novia de raab p
show the clip where Antonio says that well that's what I
enseño el clip donde Antonio dice eso
say pelusa pointed let's see
pues eso digo yo pelusa señaló a ver
how they end Javi Oy but that's going to be
cómo terminan Javi Oy pero eso va a ser
great if they fight today I heard a
buenísimo si se pelean hoy he escuchado
clip of miracle but her Let her continue with
clip de milagro pero ella Que siga con
her things she's always looking for
sus rollitos que siempre va buscando
war somewhere she wants war take
guerra por algún lado quiere guerra toma
war 240 which were 250 the 240 which are
guerra 240 que eran 250 las 240 que son
250 are 250 with a discount with a discount
250 son 250 con descuento con descuento
lady with the winds stop
señora con los ventos
Lili tells me that eh they're going to do
para me dice Lili que eh van a hacer
something about spiritual things of course they're going to
algo de cosas espirituales claro van a
do something  about spiritual things with
hacer algo de cosas espirituales con
this that oh it was going to be a
esto de que uy iba iba a ser un chiste
dark humor joke but here between gossip it can't be done let's
de humor negro pero aquí entre salseo no
see let's see it was dark humor it was
hacer a ver a ver era humor negro era
dark humor in the kids I'll say it
humor negro en la chavalería lo digo
later I mean but about spiritual things
luego o sea pero de cosas espirituales
Of course because the girl Agus who
Claro porque la la muchacha la Agus que
is very cute well when she saw
es monísima pues cuando ha visto a la
Peppa she will think that to talk to
Peppa se pensará que para hablar con
her she needs the wife that's what
ella necesita la wija eso es lo que
must have happened that's why it's going to be
habrá pasado por eso van a ser cosas
spiritual things said wow the mummy is
espirituales dicho [__] la momia esta
like balls I talk to her because
como [__] hablo con ella porque el
WhatsApp like no eh 250 I'll put it
WhatsApp como que no eh 250 te lo pongo
240 there is someone who doesn't have a lot of
240 hay que alguien que no tenga mu
life in the gossip channels well well well
viida en los canales del salseo bueno
we'll see
bueno pues ya veremos
how this turns out because the art of
e en qué queda esto porque el ar de
Troy what a provocation they are not going to
Troya vaya provocación no le irán a
clean her Hey That's good that's good
limpiar la Oye Eso es bueno eso es bueno
eh That's good that's good eh she
eh Esa es buena esa es buena eh le puede
can take Pepa and start her own
puede [__] la [__] y montar su propio
alasanas club And when they go to
club de alasanas Y que cuando vayan a
see her they clean her house no they go and
verla le limpien la casa no que vayan y
clean her house eh Hey and and How's it going with
le limpien la casa eh Oye y y Cómo va lo
putting the kitchen  Do they put it on now or
de poner la cocina se la ponen ya o
not yet? Of course, from the Freaky,
todavía no pues claro ya de los Freaky
you've been doing it for a year and a
tu hace un año y
half. Oh
medio Ay
[Music]
[Música]